<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
	<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
	<title>ECAT Announcements</title>
	<description>Here is the recent listing of Announcements</description>     
	<link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com</link>
	<item><title>Not Ready - </title><description></description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=48</link><pubDate>Jul 29 2011 12:07:20:000PM</pubDate><category></category><department></department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - New channel METV</title><description>METV is now on ch.566, soon to be added to 1898 also</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=47</link><pubDate>Jul 29 2011 12:07:15:000PM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - FLorence upgrade- benefits</title><description>Summary of Florence Benefits


&bull;	4x Fast Forward with DVR playback.
&bull;	Start Over/Enhanced menu prompt incorporated into channel banner.
&bull;	Start Over/ Look Back session bookmarking &ndash; allowing customers to resume a Start Over or Look Back session in progress.
&bull;	DVR Compensation (a.k.a. FF/REW &ldquo;jump-back&rdquo;) is now a user configurable setting.
&bull;	Whole House DVR &ndash; ability to delete (DVR) recorded programs from a client box.
&bull;	Whole House DVR interoperability &ndash; allows for Whole House functionality with various vendor boxes installed within one networked home.  (Currently WHDVR installations are limited to all Cisco boxes, or all Samsung boxes.)
</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=46</link><pubDate>Jul 19 2011 07:35:31:000AM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Toshiba Modems</title><description>Toshiba modems, 2500 and 2600, have been proven to fail. they are being removed from field when a tech finds one.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=45</link><pubDate>May 13 2011 10:29:03:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - do not use customer owned D3 modems</title><description>Why TWC does not recommend using Customer Owned Equipment
There are several reasons why using Customer Owned Equipment is not recommended:
&bull;	The equipment optimized for this new high speed product is specifically designed to complement TWC&rsquo;s unique network is not available in the retail market yet.
&bull;	The technology used to deliver these high speeds may require technical adjustments to the customers equipment to achieve peak performance and cannot be performed on retail-purchased units at this time.
&bull;	Integration of DOCSIS 3.0 and WI-FI Standard  802.11n, provides a breakthrough, future-proof wireless connection throughout the customers&rsquo; home.
&bull;	Using a Time Warner Cable provided modem is the only way to ensure the best possible experience on our network.

</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=44</link><pubDate>Apr 11 2011 01:47:58:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - clarification for ABC022 modems</title><description>We have clarification for the 2600 modems and the ABC022 Wireless phone modems are NOT D3 capable. When they were purchased they were thought to be, so were entered into the billing system with the advanced gateway port on them. When installing these modems we only need the wireless codes that correlates with the services the customer is receiving. I.E. If the customer is getting RR turbo and we add wireless we need to use the wireless turbo code. Do not add the advanced gateway code HN007 to the account, as this is to activate speeds higher than Turbo and these modems are not compatible for those speeds.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=43</link><pubDate>Apr  8 2011 01:25:55:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - FIS codes</title><description>All new FIS codes have been rolled out, few changes coming with SRO\\\&#039;s that need to be brought back for our use.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=42</link><pubDate>Mar 29 2011 11:24:33:000AM</pubDate><category>7</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - D3 modems</title><description>We have a good supply of D3 modems so we can install D3 modems for Signature Home customers in any area whether we offer D3 service or not.  

 

We have a good supply of D3 modems so we can install D3 modems for Signature Home customers in any area whether we offer D3 service or not.  

 

We have a good supply of D3 modems so we can install D3 modems for Signature Home customers in any area whether we offer D3 service or not.  

 

There is a good supply of D3 modems,install D3 modems in all Signature Home installs in all areas,  Feb 25,2011</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=41</link><pubDate>Feb 25 2011 06:53:22:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - New converters orders</title><description>going forward,  all new converters ordered into the division will not have PIP capability</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=40</link><pubDate>Feb 17 2011 09:27:30:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - WHDVR- equipment used</title><description>We have been working with techs, the equipment can be added thru Arris, not having problems with it.  If anything it may be training.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=39</link><pubDate>Feb 17 2011 09:26:40:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - FCC mandates letter to be sent for change of BILL TO address</title><description>Corporate is working to build a program that will automatically cause a letter to be generated to a customers old address when they request a change to their \&quot;Bill To\&quot; address.  This is a new FCC mandate.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=38</link><pubDate>Feb 15 2011 03:50:25:000PM</pubDate><category>7</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Whole House DVR</title><description>Whole House DVR is being advertised as available everywhere in the East Region to customers via the Channel You website.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=37</link><pubDate>Feb 15 2011 03:05:02:000PM</pubDate><category>1</category><department>7</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - tech\&#039;s  service/supoort DL</title><description>Techs can use DL-ALB-DISPATCH-SUPPORT as well as calling for service and support in dispatch.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=36</link><pubDate>Feb  3 2011 07:32:36:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Dynamic routing</title><description>Dynamic routing is starting, Tuesday, Feb 1st.   Techs will see 2 jobs at a time, there will probably be questions.   We are here to help you in anyway.   </description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=35</link><pubDate>Jan 31 2011 03:56:21:000PM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Albany County nodes - Wednesday - Bethlehem </title><description>Albany county nodes will be renamed starting Wednesday.  Bethlehem hub will first to be renamed.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=21</link><pubDate>Jan 31 2011 09:40:12:000AM</pubDate><category>6</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Washington Ave Node Renaming Starts Today.</title><description>Washington Ave Node Renaming Starts Today.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=34</link><pubDate>Jan 31 2011 09:38:46:000AM</pubDate><category>7</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Direct Sales Customers</title><description>Please be advised, the Regional Outbound Center does not support the Direct Sales department.  Any Albany DSR inquiries should be forwarded to Jamie Stewart(DSR Manager) or Cindy McCardle and Karen Lemay (DSR Admins.)  Thanks</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=33</link><pubDate>Jan 28 2011 12:59:38:000PM</pubDate><category>8</category><department>10</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Node Name Conversion - Washington Ave, Birch Hill, and Berne</title><description>Washington Ave, Birch Hill, and Berne nodes are set to be renamed starting Monday 1/31.  The schedule would be Monday, Wednesday, Friday respectively.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=32</link><pubDate>Jan 27 2011 03:31:01:000PM</pubDate><category>6</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Credit Card Info</title><description>Just a reminder that we should never be writing a customer\&#039;s credit card information anywhere-not on paper, not in microsoft word, etc.  We need to enter it directly into ICOM\&#039;s only.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=31</link><pubDate>Jan 27 2011 10:43:33:000AM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>5</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - Corporate Billing Proposed Change to PWS Codes - No Date Yet</title><description>The corporate billing support team is proposing to add a whole new set of PWS codes to the billing system. These codes would duplicate most of the current standard codes and would add the S category.  This would give the ability of not having to split the S category off into separate work orders.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=30</link><pubDate>Jan 27 2011 10:08:36:000AM</pubDate><category>Billing System</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - 4 Day Sale!</title><description>4 Day Sale

Eligible $33 x 3 Customers get DVR service for free for 12 months

 

January 28th  - January 31st, the sweeteners go back to what they were before the 4 Day Sale  

HBO for free for 3 months &amp; DVR service for free for 3 months

</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=23</link><pubDate>Jan 26 2011 03:33:05:000PM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>2</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Pac supervisor</title><description>any issues concerning phone provisioning, or need questions answered from PAC please direct them to Hiliary White or Brett Johnson</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=26</link><pubDate>Jan 26 2011 09:44:25:000AM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>2</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Customer Type \''O\''</title><description>We are now using a new customer type.  Any account that is marked as customer type \''O\'' is an  account that is  being investigated by the security operations team for fraudulent activity.  Any questions or concerns regarding these accounts should be directed to Joe Nowak at #528-1831, Ralph Campo ext 8916 or Geoff Madaio ext 3105.

</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=25</link><pubDate>Jan 26 2011 09:14:20:000AM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>5</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - wireless phone modems (ABC022)</title><description>Wireless phone modems are out in the field (ABC022)
Contact tech supervisors or training dept for specs</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=11</link><pubDate>Jan 25 2011 05:46:05:000PM</pubDate><category>6</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - Soft Disco\''s on GIA accounts. </title><description>For cycles 28,1,2, 6,and,9 we will be pushing up any phone account to past 1/14/11 for their soft disco. Pending and Field discos orders during this time will be lite. W/Os after the 14th may be higher than normal.   </description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=22</link><pubDate>Jan 25 2011 03:32:09:000PM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>5</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - trouble call time</title><description>starting Jan 27th, trouble call will be set at 70 minutes, or 14 points</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=16</link><pubDate>Jan 20 2011 02:53:01:000PM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - New Item Types</title><description>  Item Type                          Description
 
1) ABD2600 - Ubee Wireless Modem Turbo Compatible (looks identical to the Ambit Router ABD2700 best way to tell them apart is the wireless has an antenna) 
 
2) ABC020 - Ubee Wireless 2 port MTA
 
3) ABC034 - Ubee 2 port MTA
 
4) CI8642S - Cisco Moca HD DVR (looks identical to the 8640)
 
5) CI4642 - Cisco Moca Digital Box (looks Identical to the 4640)
 
6) SM3262S - Samsung Moca Digital (looks identical to the 3260)
 
7) SM3272 - Samsung Moca DVR (looks identical to the 3270)
 
8) SBV5322 - Motorola 4 port Commercial Modem
 
9) U3611W - Ubee D3 Commercial Wireless Modem.
 
10) SBG6580 - Motorola D3 Wireless Modem</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=15</link><pubDate>Jan 19 2011 08:50:15:000AM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>12</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Node Renaming</title><description>All nodes in the Albany market are going to be renamed. This is a regional engineering project. Albany county nodes have already been changed on the maps and Icoms will be updated next week.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=14</link><pubDate>Jan 18 2011 04:25:50:000PM</pubDate><category>6</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - 3250 HD boxes</title><description>All 3250s will be pulled out of tech stock ASAP.

 

Techs should not use 3250s if they still have them

 

Techs will have plenty of other model numbers to work with W/O the 3250s

 

Schenectady will be the only system using 3250s because you are performing a test with them
</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=13</link><pubDate>Jan 18 2011 01:05:24:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - Stand Alone Whole House DVR set to launch at the end of January</title><description>To start the training process for the Stand Alone Whole House DVR, Tech ops and Care are being assigned E-modules in the LMS. This is going to be followed by class room training.
The LMS codes for the E-Mods are CUS71114LDI for care and TEC65021LDI for Tech Ops</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=9</link><pubDate>Jan 11 2011 04:00:33:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>2</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - cod at door</title><description>techs are only allowed to except payment in form of credit cards and checks, to be called in to dispatch for payment thru PCI in icoms</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=8</link><pubDate>Jan 10 2011 03:28:30:000PM</pubDate><category>2</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - modems</title><description>the ABC034 modem is  out in the field now,  it is not a wireless modem, phone only.    not to be confused with the ABC022. </description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=7</link><pubDate>Jan  7 2011 01:59:48:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - modems</title><description>new abc034 modems,  they are NOT wireless and not to be confused with the abc022,  which are wireless </description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=6</link><pubDate>Jan  7 2011 10:28:37:000AM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item><item><title>Not Ready - Work Order Accuracy (WOA) is being update to fix Dir listing issue.</title><description>A modification to work order accuracy has been tested and is ready for use in the live system. This update verifies that address on the house matches the address in the customer\''s DIR listing. If not, you must go back and update that information.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=5</link><pubDate>Jan  7 2011 09:34:47:000AM</pubDate><category>5</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - Directory Listing for phone customers</title><description>Currently we have many customers who\''s Directory listing information is wrong. Specifically, the Address in the dir listing shows a phone number instead of a customers house number (address). A ticket is open with Convergys to fix.</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=4</link><pubDate>Jan  7 2011 09:32:27:000AM</pubDate><category>Customer Info</category><department>6</department></item><item><title>Ready to Launch - No Longer Carrying Netgear Routers @ The Cable Stores</title><description>The Cable Stores will be moving away from carrying Netgear wireless routers at the counter. We have stopped purchasing new Netgear Wireless Routers for the time being. We will have a limited stock of units to use as necessary, but we will no longer be able to provide Netgear Routers to customers who do not intend to use it with a Phone Modem. 

We are hoping to see new hardware in early 2011 that will eliminate the need for a separate wireless router for our beloved phone customers. Until that time, we need to ask all \''customer interactive\'' employees (Call Center and Tech Ops)  to no longer set the expectation that a customer should come in to the Cable Store to pick up a Netgear Wireless Router. Most locations are completely out of stock at this time.

Existing customers with a standard Cable Modem may bring their equipment to the Cable Stores to swap for a Wireless Modem, should they wish to go wireless.
</description><link>http://ecat.alb.twcable.com/index.php?id=1</link><pubDate>Dec 17 2010 04:55:08:000PM</pubDate><category>4</category><department>9</department></item></channel>
</rss>